求你
Please.
不要
No.
《黑吃黑》第三季 第七集
Banshee S03E07
加油  查理  揍他
Go, Charlie! Hit him!
狠揍他  哥们
Kick his ass, man!
-小心  -我看不下去了
- Watch your back! - I can't watch this.
-漂亮  -蒂法  我要回家
- Yeah! - Deva, I'm gonna go home.
蒂法
Deva.
比蒂  你想怎么样随便  我不走
Beaty, do whatever the hell you want. I'm staying.
行  我走了
Fine. I'm out of here.
-打啊  -真是好样的
- Do it! - Hey, that's my boy right there!
去他妈的  我们动真格的
Fuck this shit! Let's get real.
第二轮
Round two!
给他点颜色瞧瞧
Oh! Light him up!
漂亮
Oh-ho! That's it!
再来一下
Yeah! Again!
你他妈来干什么
What the fuck are you doing here?
我认识个线人  能帮忙找到切顿
I know a CI that can help find Chayton.
是以前红骨帮的  价格会很高
A former Redbone. Price tag's gonna be steep.
不管多钱  我都给
Whatever it costs, I'll get the money.
通知你的线人吧
Call your informant.
胡德
Hood.
当时有机会  我本应该开枪的
Should have pulled the trigger when I had a chance.
当时旧情一时难舍
It's hard to shake all that history in one moment.
相信我  我懂
Trust me, I know.
道格拉斯·斯托上...
Colonel Douglas Sto--
我操
Motherfuck!
直接用斯托的录音不就行了吗
Wouldn't it be easier to just use a recording of Stowe's voice?
不行
No, it would not.
斯托的语音识别系统
Stowe's voice recognition system
能识别大部分数字模拟声音
can identify most digital forgeries.
道格拉斯·斯托上校
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
但无法识别我的
But not mine.
行了  我们可以动手了
All right. Then we good to go.
还差得远呢
We ain't even close.
那个基地跟前三次
That base looks the same as it did
你看的时候  一模一样
the last three times you checked it.
不  就是不对劲
No, something ain't right.
可能是你哪根筋搭错了吧
That would be your nerves.
别闹  我的筋都是焊接好的
Please, I do not do nerves.
你想知道我在想什么吗
Do you want to know what I think?
你知道我对那个问题的答案
You do know my answer to that question
永远不会变  对吧
never changes, right?
打消疑虑方法只有一个
There's only one way to lay those doubts to rest.
而且不是在这里傻坐着把自己逼疯
And it ain't sitting around here driving yourself crazy.
仅此而已
That's all.
别叫  不然杀了你
Scream and I'll kill you.
这里还有别人吗
Is there anyone else in the house?
我们走
Let's go.
我要向山举目
I will lift up mine eyes unto the hills
我的帮助从何而来
from whence cometh my help.
我的帮助从造天地的
My help cometh from the Lord
耶和华而来
which made heaven and earth.
他必不叫你的脚摇动
He will not suffer thy foot to be moved.
保护你的必不打盹
He will keepeth thee and will not slumber.
保护以色列的
Behold, He that keepeth Israel
也不打盹  也不睡觉
shall neither slumber nor sleep.
兄弟们  如果有基督徒偶尔不慎犯了罪
Brothers, if anyone is caught in any transgression,
你们灵命坚强的人
you who are spiritual should restore him
就应该温和耐心地纠正他
in a spirit of gentleness.
欢迎  凯
Welcome, Kai.
同时也要提高警觉
Keep watch on yourself lest you,
免受诱惑  远离犯罪
too, be tempted.
如果有人自以为是
If anyone thinks they are something when they are not,
他们就是自欺欺人
they deceive themselves.
人人需要醒己之行为
Each one should test their own actions.
之后便可对己引以为傲
Then they can take pride in themselves alone
不拿自己与他人作比
without comparing themselves to someone else.
每个人都要负起自己的责任
For each should carry their own load.
那人身高约一米九三  满身部落刺青
Look, the man is 6'4" and covered in tribal tats.
我不信没人看到过他
I can't believe no one has seen him.
不  我理解
No, I-- I understand.
好  如果有任何消息  请马上通知我
Okay, but, look, if you hear anything, you know where to find me.
谢谢
Thank you.
有出警吗
Any calls?
没有  漫长的一天
No, sir. Slow day.
你好  我是艾米丽·洛特斯  有事请留言
Hi, you've reached Emily Lotus. Please leave a message.
你好  是我
Uh, hi. It's me.
又是我
Again.
好久没你的消息了  所以...
Haven't heard from you, so...
我知道你现在不太想见到我  但是...
Look, I know I'm not your most favorite person right now, but...
我刚刚还在想我们的事然后  谢谢
you know, I was just thinking about us and I-- thanks.
请尽快回我电话
Uh, yeah, please return my call at your earliest convenience.
费城来的朋友告诉我  你对之前
Our friend from Philadelphia tells me you're a little confused
弗拉奇尔先生叫他转达的提议不太明白
about the offer he delivered from Mr. Frazier.
他们从我们的竞争对手那里买货
They were buying from our competition
而你要用降价来奖励他们
and you want to reward that with a discount?
我已经同意了弗拉奇尔的条件
I already agreed to Frazier's terms.
立刻终止所有与萨尔瓦多人的交易
Stop all sales to the Salvadorans immediately.
懂了吗
Is that understood?
讲讲理吧
懂了吗  丽贝卡
Is that understood, Rebecca?
你叔叔知道你来这里了吗
Does your uncle know you're here?
不关你的事
That's not your concern.
没有什么不关我的事
Everything is my concern.
你说  我为什么要跟
So tell me, why am I having a conversation
断了我货的家伙的侄女谈话呢
with the niece of the man who cut me off?
我来修正那个暂时的错误
I'm here to correct that temporary error in judgment.
你凭什么认为我会从你手上买货
What makes you think I'd ever buy from you?
因为你不买就太傻了
Because you'd be a fool not to.
据说弗拉奇尔正在试图
Word on the street is that Frazier
让你歇业
is trying to put you out of business.
你管不住你的地盘
You've lost control of your street corners,
和你的人了
your raves.
几周之内  你就会彻底关门
In a couple of weeks, you'll be shut down completely.
而我能让你重返赛场
I can get you back in the game.
你能
Can you?
我们开始时慢一点
We'll start slow.
每周两公斤  每公斤七千块
Two kilos per week at 7,000 per.
每公斤四千
4,000 per key.
六千
6,000.
要么你也可以去求弗拉奇尔赏你块骨头
Or maybe you can convince Frazier to throw you a bone.
你们交情不浅  不是吗
You guys go way back, don't you?
我喜欢你  小妞
I like you, chica.
真心的
I really do.
但要是你敢耍我
But if you fuck me,
你叔叔就只能见到你的残片了
your uncle will be scooping you up in tiny little pieces.
我很期待与您达成长期而富有成效的合作  莫拉莱斯先生
I look forward to a long and fruitful relationship, Mr. Morales.
叫我赫克托
Hector.
顺便说一声  我一直在注意联调局的动静
Just so you know, I have been monitoring the FBI's progress.
谢顿还是没有音讯
Chayton is still off the grid.
可胡德警官  就不同了
Sheriff Hood, however, is not.
费列罗队长起草了一份正式的意见书
Captain Ferillo has filed a formal complaint.
Captain Ferillo 警匪美剧《希尔街的布鲁斯》中的角色
你一直盯着热那亚营呢吗
Have you been watching Camp Genoa?
你听见我刚才的话了吗
Did you hear what I just said?
听见了  去他的费列罗
I did. Fuck Ferillo.
有什么需要我小心的吗
Is there anything I should worry about?
恕我直言  我们都应当谨慎一点
With all due respect, we should all be a little worried.
我想把活推迟
I want to delay the job.
基地这周末就关了
That base will be shut down by the end of the week.
现在不做就没机会了  贾伯
It's now or never, Job.
那恐怕就没机会了
Well, then I guess it's never.
什么
What?
亲  怎样的你我都见过
Baby, I have seen every side of you there is.
鲁莽的  二缺的  特别是固执的
Reckless, dumb, and especially stubborn.
但我从没见你这样过
But I ain't never seen this.
你陷得太深了
You in the deep end.
要是你还不能让自己脱离困境
If you don't keep your head above water,
你会拉着我们一起沉没的
you going to drag the rest of us down there with you.
我们要干这个活
We're doing the fucking job.
今晚就干
We're doing it tonight.
那祝你们好运
Well, good luck with that.
贾伯
Job.
你曾问我需要什么
You asked me what I needed.
现在  就这事
Right now, this is it.
好吧
Fine.
我去洗漱一下
I'll go get cleaned up.
拍嫌犯照片的时候希望能好看点
Might as well look pretty for my mug shot.
按住
Hold.
好了
Okay.
你不怕我
You're not afraid of me?
不怕
No.
你应该怕我
You should be.
我把丈夫和孩子都埋葬了
I buried a husband and a child.
甚至曾觉得没有生存下去的意义
There are days I don't think I have anything left to live for anyway.
她又赢不了选美比赛
Well, she ain't gonna win no beauty contests.
谢谢
Thank you.
他怎么样了
So how is he?
和以前一样
Same as ever.
别担心  他还是很可靠的
Well, don't worry, we can count on him.
女服务员到了吗
Has the waitress checked in?
卡莉还没报道  但她会来的
Carrie hasn't checked in yet, but she will.
她最好有好状态
She best be on her game.
瞧瞧那两个人  你说不准还以为
You'd think we were knocking over a motherfucking 7-Eleven
咱们是去抢便利店呢
the way these two are acting.
你知道吗  贾伯  你操太多心了
You know what, Job? You worry too much.
总得有个人来操心吧
Well, somebody's got to.
咱们来看看
Let's see what we got.
很好
That's good.
比蒂  怎么了
Hey, Beaty. What's up?
什么
What?
她在哪
Where is she?
-你确定是这里吗  -没错
- You sure this is the place? - Yes.
我能让你待在车里别过来吗
Any chance I can convince you to stay out here?
那好吧
All right, then.
蒂法
Deva!
-搞什么  -马上跟我们回家
- What the fuck? - We're going home now.
你们在这干什么
What the hell are you guys doing here?
-别让我说第二遍  -她哪都不去
- I'm not gonna tell you again. - She's not going anywhere.
-你还是闭嘴吧  -我才不信呢
- Okay, you need to shut your mouth. - I don't believe this.
你们不能突然就决定管我了
You guys can't just decide when to give a shit.
-蒂法  -不  我要留下来
- Deva! - No, I'm staying.
你也听到了  她哪都不去  伙计
You heard her, she's not going anywhere, man.
给我让开
Get out of my way.
这可是我的地盘  老家伙
You're on my property, old man.
你还是赶紧滚吧
And you need to fuck off now.
好吧
Okay.
深呼吸  咱们好好考虑考虑
Let's just all take a deep breath and think about this.
你会后悔的
You shouldn't have done that.
-戈登  -查理  求你不要
- Gordon! - Charlie, no! Please!
-求你别  -蒂法  你他妈闭嘴
- Please, don't. - Deva, shut the fuck up!
你有胆量开枪吗  小子
You man enough to pull that trigger, son?
我要杀了你
I'll kill you.
爸爸
Dad.
那就少废话开枪吧
Then stop talking and do it.
我发誓我会开枪  狗娘养的
I swear, I'll shoot you, motherfucker.
开枪啊
Pull it.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
蒂法  过来
Deva, come here!
我操  是市长
Holy fuck. That's the mayor.
你没事吧
You okay?
我不怎么在外面吃饭
I don't eat out much.
老实说  我自己也很久没出来吃饭了
To be honest, it's been a while for me, too.
我都忘了高跟鞋有多折磨人了
Forgotten what medieval torture high heels can be.
你美极了  艾米丽
You look beautiful, Emily.
我也好久没听过这种话了
It's also been some time since I've heard that.
谢谢
Thank you.
敬我们都走出了舒适区
Well, here is to getting outside of our comfort zones.
你的笑容很美
You have a nice smile.
我觉得很少有人能看到你舒展笑颜
I bet not many people get to see that.
没错  我觉得不多
No. No, I guess not.
我知道把自己隔绝起来是什么感受
Yeah, I know what it's like to put up walls.
你的侄女  瑞贝卡
Your niece, Rebecca--
她跟你一起住多久了
how long has she been living with you?
不久
Not long.
她惹上了些麻烦  需要有人指点迷津
She was in trouble. She needed guidance.
她现在应该靠她自己了
And the time is coming for her to be on her own.
可能这样最好
It's probably for the best.
你觉得其他家长也是这么管孩子的吗
So do you think that's what other family interventions are like?
希望吧
I hope so.
凭什么乐子都让咱们俩享受了呢
I mean, why should we be the only ones having all the fun?
你想要来一点还是来一大杯
You want a small pour or big?
我不喝
Neither.
我们做得很好
We did good out there.
没错
Yeah, we did.
你去哪了
Where were you?
去兜了兜风  希望你别介意
I went for a little ride. Hope you don't mind.
如果你在测试我的耐心  那就太不明智了
It would be unwise to test me.
做梦都不敢
I wouldn't dream of it.
你的车没油了
You're out of gas.
那...
So...
回见
See you around?
好的
Yeah.
Okay.
晚安  戈登
Good night, Gordon.
晚安
Good night.
你可以开走我丈夫的卡车
You can take my husband's truck.
自从他去世后我就没有开过它
I haven't driven it since he passed.
你不能逃避死亡
You can't hide from the dead.
那不是你正在做的事情吗
Isn't that what you're doing?
丽莎  你在里面吗
Lisa, you in there?
你骗我
You lied to me.
不  他只是邻居
No, he is just a neighbor who--
他会时不时的来看看我
he just comes to check on me now and then.
打发他走
Get rid of him.
-你在这儿  宝贝  -嗨
- There you are, sunshine. - Hey.
玛格丽特做好了晚餐  三人份的
Margaret's fixing dinner. She's got the table set for three.
谢谢  文斯  不用了
Thanks, Vince. No, thanks.
来吧  她做了她最拿手的鸡肉和饼干
Come on, she's making her world-famous chicken and biscuits.
我说了不用
I said no.
一切都好吧
Is everything all right?
是的  我很好  我只是
No, I'm fine. I just--
我只想独处一会儿
I just needed a little time alone, that's all.
抱歉
Sorry.
-好吧  -谢谢
- Okay. - Thanks.
不  不
No, no, no!
天哪
Oh, my...
我们动手吧
Let's go to work.
糖果
Sugar.
醒醒
Wake up.
再调试一次
Run through it again.
我们已经试了六次了
We've already done it six times.
那我们就做第七次
And we are going to do it a seventh time.
如果你能数到那么多的话
If you can count that high.
胡德
Hood.
你
You.
卡莉
Carrie.
满意了吗
Satisfied?
还没  给我看看热那亚基地的保安摄像头
No, show me the security cam from Genoa.
实时的
Real time.
再给我看看循环画面
Now show me the loop.
好  还有其他的吗
Okay, anything else?
-是的  -什么
- Yeah. - What?
我要把这些隐蔽好的摄像头
I'm going to be leaving these cover cams
放在我们潜入和撤退的路线上
at our entry and exit routes.
好像我现在看的还不够似的
Like I don't have enough to watch.
我可不愿意冒险
I ain't taking no chances.
如果你看见任何可疑人物
If you see anybody or anything that don't belong there,
可要张开尊口告诉我们
you open that big-ass mouth of yours and make some noise.
好的
Yeah.
三  二  一
Three, two, one.
好的
Okay.
大家都准备好了吗
Everybody ready?
是的
Yeah.
-是的  -我们动手吧
- Yeah. - Let's do it.
得安静谨慎了
Time for some peace and quiet.
炸药装好了
Explosives up.
好了
All right.
看你的了  糖果
It's all yours, Sugar.
放马过来吧
Bringing it up.
这他妈不动啊
It ain't gonna fucking give.
妈的
God damn!
妈蛋
Motherfuck!
好的  西边没动静
Okay, all quiet on the western front.
容易的活已经完了  我们进去吧
That was the easy part. We're in.
好  我这就下来
Okay, I'm on my way down.
跟着我
On me.
开始吧
Let's do it.
好的  好的  看起来不错
All right. All right. Looking good.
军械库
道格拉斯·斯托上校
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
把手放中央
道格拉斯·斯托上校
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
安全了
Clear.
你有三分钟准备
You got three minutes to set up.
-别让我等着  -明白
- Don't keep me waiting. - I got it.
去电脑室的走廊是空的
Okay, the hallway to the computer room is wide open.
尽管走就好
Just keep moving.
安全警告
限制区域
闲人免进
热那亚营
美国海军陆战队
登录:认证成功
安全演算覆盖:运行中
一旦我开始演算  你有12分钟行动
Once I initiate the algorithm, you're gonna have 12 minutes.
准备好了  就等你了
Ready when you are.
准备开始
Get ready.
三  二  一  行动
Three, two, one, move.
格式化中
求你了
Please.
求你了  不要
Please, don't.
求你了
Please.
这是什么
What the...?
格式化中
求你了
Please.
见鬼  贾伯现在在计算机房需要帮助
Shit! Job needs help in the computer room now.
有人能听见我说话吗
Anybody hearing me?
有人听到吗
Anybody hear me?
我不能过去  时间不够了
I can't. I'm running out of time.
他他妈的在干吗
What the fuck is he doing?
你他妈的去哪了
Where the fuck were you?!
操
Fuck.
你有两分钟
You got two minutes.
准备抬屁股走吧  老家伙
Wake your ass up, old man.
我们马上就回去
We flying to you.
糟了  这可不是什么好事
Oh, shit. Now, that can't be good.
大家听好
All right, listen up, people.
那个老大刚刚到基地了
The big boss man has just arrived on base.
道格拉斯·斯通上校
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
菲茨帕克里特  我的身份验证无效
Fitzpatrick, my ID isn't working.
我没办法进入办公室
I can't get into my office.
我的记录显示你划卡进了军械库
I have you swiped into the armory.
马上派一队人去军械库
Send a team to the armory now.
-多少人  -所有人
- How many? - All of them.
快  宝贝们  大家动作要快
Come on, baby. Keep it moving, people.
大队人马就要过去了
It's about to get real crowded down there.
宝贝  我们得走了
Baby, we got to move!
该死
Shit.
我真他妈的不敢相信  有人重置了密码
I don't fucking believe it. Someone reset the codes.
把这破门打开
Open the fucking door!
开了
Got it.
快
Go!
该死
Shit.
道格拉斯·斯通上校
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
见鬼
Oh, shit.
再试一次
Try again.
道格拉斯·斯通上校
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
怎么回事
What's wrong?
我他妈怎么知道
How the fuck should I know?
道格拉斯·斯通上校
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
-贾伯  快离开  -把他们找出来
- Job, move! - Find them.
别  别  他们会听到的
No, no, don't, don't. They're gonna hear us!
-操  -快走
- Fuck! - Move!
快  快  快
Come on, come on, come on.
快跑  跑  跑
Let's go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
快  快  快
Come on, come on, come on.
走
Go!
操
Fuck!
快  宝贝  快  就现在
Come on, baby. Come on, now.
你在这都干了什么
What did you do here?
你这个淘气的小婊子
You sly little cunt.
拿着这个袋子
Take the bags!
快走
Go!
贾伯
Job!
-糖果  -拿到了
- Sugar! - Got it. Ah!
好了  上来  给我吧
All right, come on, bring it.
拿到了
Got it.
来吧  宝贝
Come on, baby.
炸掉它  趁现在
Blow it now!
有点不对劲
There's something wrong.
不对劲  不对劲
Something's wrong. Something's wrong.
检查下雷管
Check the detonator.
-炸了它  -炸吧
- Blow it! - Just do it.
-快炸  -炸啊
- Blow it! - Do it!
操
Damn.
-好了  -他在哪儿
- All right. - Where is he?
如果炸的时候他还在下面
If he was down there when it blew,
那他没时间躲开爆炸
he didn't have time to clear the blast.
我们得撤了
We got to move.
等着
Wait!
天哪
Oh, my God.
操
Shit!
快点  宝贝  我们走了
Come on, baby, we going!
各位还喘着气呢
Everybody still breathing back there?
是
Yeah.
二手车市场
卡迪
-你好  布罗克  -艾米丽
- Hello, Brock. - Oh, Emily.
没想到你会接电话
I didn't think you'd pick up.
邻居说警察来我家了
Neighbors told me the police were at the house.
是  一直没你消息  我很担心
Well, yeah, I hadn't heard from you. I was worried.
拜托  艾米丽  选谁也别选他啊
God, Emily, please. Anybody but him.
-布罗克  -不
- Brock. - No.
这事不是咱俩的事
Look, this isn't about you and me anymore.
-这事关系到你的安全  -我很好
- This is about your safety. - I'm fine.
也许现在是  但你在玩火
Yeah, maybe now. But, I mean, you know, you're tempting fate.
听我说  你必须
Listen to me. You have got to
离那个男人越远越好
get as far away from that man as possible.
你不懂  我们之间有种默契
You don't understand. We have a connection.
默契  不  你知道那是什么吗
Connection? No, no. You know what it is?
你认为你能改变他  就像你试着改变我
You think you can fix him the same way you tried to fix me.
-布罗克  再见  -喂  小艾
- Good-bye, Brock. - Hello? Em?
喂  艾米丽
Hello? Emily?
我去
God!
西沃恩·凯莉  副警长
通缉令
胡德在哪儿
Where's Hood?
你们知道这是在庆祝吧
You guys do know this is a celebration, right?
我要回家了
I got to get home.
你干得很不错  糖果
You did great, Sugar.
我知道
I know.
我不知道你俩咋了
Look, I don't know what's going on between you two,
-但不管咋样  -我分心了
- but whatever it is-- - I got distracted.
你害我们都很危险
You put us all at motherfucking risk.
-你让我一个人  -贾伯
- You left me hanging-- - Job!
别说了
Don't.
这
It--
干杯
L'chaim.
不用了
Keep it.
我说服我的线人该点良心了
I convinced my CI it was time to grow a conscience.
切顿在哪儿
Where's Chayton?
前往路易斯安那州
Headed to Louisiana.
那里有个被部落驱逐的人组成的组织
There's a group of tribal outcasts
在新奥尔良
based in New Orleans.
他们自称为是18号牢笼
They call themselves the 18th Ward.
你要去吗
You're going down there?
是
Yes.
你找到他之后打算怎么做
What are you gonna do when you find him?
做你做不到的
What you couldn't.
听着  我知道这对你来说很痛苦
Look, I know this is hard for you.
不  我认识的男孩已经死了
No, the boy I knew is dead.
在树林里的那天  我直视他的双眼
That day in the woods, I looked into his eyes
而他可以不假思索的杀了我
and he would have killed me without a second thought.
不管他曾经怎样  现在已是个冷血杀手
Whoever he once was, he's a stone-cold killer now
他需要被制伏
and he needs to be put down.
我只是不想亲眼看到这一幕
I just can't be there to watch it happen.
警长  小心点
Take care of yourself, Sheriff.
布罗克
Hey, Brock.
替我挡着点
Cover for me.
抱歉  做不到
Sorry, can't do it.
啥
What?
因为我要和你一起去新奥尔良
Because I'm going with you to New Orleans.
我开车
I'll drive.
不是我的错  就是你的错
It's not my fault. It's your fucking fault.
不是我的错
It's not my fault.
采取了预防措施
Precautions were taken.
怪他们  就是你的错
Blame them. It's your fucking fault.
这不可能  我没有
This isn't possible. I did not--